chatroulettehalloffame.com 2012-10-22

# Privacy | Chatroulette Hall of Fame

Your privacy is incredibly important to us. To ensure and protect your privacy we offer this notice explaining our online information practices and the option you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To render this notification easy to find, we make it vacant on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet. Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to put advertise on this site. 

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html The track of visitors through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies. 

Other Third Party ad servers or ads networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, Chatroulettehof.com has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers. 

Collection of Personal Information When visiting Chatroulettehof.com, the IP address used to access the site could be logged along with the dates and times of access. This kind of information is exclusively used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. We assure that any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable informations. 

Backlinks to third party Websites We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own. 

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of Chatroulettehof.com then you may contact us at masterchat@chatroulettehof.com Thank you.
